You just said that you spent a lot of
time alone.
さっき一人で過ごす時間が
長いって言ってたよね
Yeah. And sometimes you got to
do that
うん
時には地元の仲間とでも
even with the people you come from.
距離を置かなきゃいけないこともある
Because I feel safe alone.
一人の方が安全だと感じるからさ
I feel like me chilling with you might
be a liability for me.
お前とつるむこと自体が
俺にはリスクかもしれねぇ
Just because we just live two
different lifestyles
生き方が全然違うし
and I think differently from ground
up than you,
根本から考え方も違うから
you might put me in harm's way and
not even realize it.
知らないうちに俺を
危険な目に遭わせるかもしれない
So cut them people off.
じゃあそういう奴らとは縁を切ると
No, but that's you.
いや、お前のことだって
It could be you. It could be you,
Charlamagne, right now.
お前かもしれないし
今ここにいるシャーラメインかもな
Charlamagne ain't gonna put you in
a place
シャーラメインがお前を
where you feel like your life is
threatened. No.
命の危険にさらすことはねぇよ
Envy ain't gonna put you in a place
エンヴィーだって
where you feel like your life is
threatened. Intentionally.
命の危険にさらしたりしねぇ
わざとはな
No, we got too much to lose.
しないしない、俺らも失うもんが多すぎる
I don't want to sound tough or none
of that,
イキってるように
聞こえたくはないけど
but I'm dramatically different from
the average person. You feel me?
俺は普通の人とは
全然違うんだよ
It's to a certain extent, the security
don't even got it
ある程度までいくと
セキュリティでさえ
in him nine times out of ten. Like,
you feel me?
10回中9回は
そこまでの覚悟ないからな
What I'ma do? Like, I'ma put you to
the test.
俺がどうするかって？
お前を試すんだよ
Go in the street and let me see you
in extreme situation. You feel me?
ストリートに出て
極限状態のお前を見せてみろって
Sometimes you got to fight fire
with fire.
時には毒を以て毒を制す
しかねぇんだよ
Sometimes I be around the bros and
I be like,
仲間といる時も
bro, y'all annoying me. You feel me?
「お前らうぜぇよ」って言うしな
And they know that. They know that.
We talk to them.
あいつらもわかってる
ちゃんと話してるし
I be like, I love y'all, bro. I want y'all
to do better, bro.
「愛してるよ、お前らには
もっとちゃんとしてほしいんだよ」
But y'all is annoying. Y'all in the way.
You feel me?
「でもうぜぇし、邪魔なんだよ」って
But to a certain extent, you just kind
of like, you need to balance it.
でもある程度は
バランス取らなきゃいけない
It's just because I can't change. This
is like my life.
俺は変われないからさ
これが俺の人生なんだよ
Like, this is like, you feel me? You
know, but this is how I feel.
わかるだろ？
これが俺の気持ちなんだよ
You'll be singing a totally different
tune in five years. Guaranteed.
5年後には全然違うこと言ってるよ
絶対な
Hopefully so. You feel me?
だといいけどな